intimissimi.com 2015-02-13

# Privacy - Intimissimi

Welcome to the Calzedonia Group websites. 

Hereafter, you will find information on how we use the personal data of the individuals who navigate on our websites. If you would like to have a more complete picture of the principles that we follow in the management of our websites and in the protection of your information, we invite you to read the **General Conditions** for use of the websites. 

The following information applies to the domains and sub-domains registered for each of the trademarks and companies belonging to the Calzedonia Group, such as CALZEDONIA, INTIMISSIMI, TEZENIS, FALCONERI, HOTEL VERONESI LA TORRE, SIGNORVINO, AGRIBEL. We inform you that this privacy policy refers only to the sites used by the domains and sub-domains registered for each of the trademarks and companies of the Calzedonia Group, and not for any other websites which may be visited by the users via links. 

We reserve the right to update the contents of this screen periodically. We therefore invite you to review our privacy policy regularly so as to remain updated with respect to any changes that may have been made since the last time you looked. 

To find out more about privacy and the use of your personal data, select the area of your interest, depending on whether you are merely a visitor or a user of web services subject to registration. 

##   
FOR THOSE WHO VISIT THE CALZEDONIA GROUP WEBSITES 

This screen describes a few rules of management of the Calzedonia Group websites, with reference to the personal data of the users who visit them. These rules apply in all the cases in which you access our websites, navigating on the screens without registering or completing or entering data on web forms. 

By visiting the websites of the Calzedonia Group, you accept the terms and conditions detailed hereafter. If you consider that you cannot accept these terms we ask you not to access or use the contents and services offered through our websites. 

##  FOR THOSE WHO USE WEB SERVICES REQUIRING PERSONAL DATA   
(Information about the use of the personal data provided pursuant to and by the effects of art. 13, L.D. 196/03) 

###  What types of data do we collect during the user’s navigation? 

While you visit our websites, the information systems assigned to their operation normally acquire certain data the transmission of which is implicit and necessary for the internet to function. This is information that is not collected to be associated with identified persons but that by nature, after being processed and associated with data in the possession of others, could make it possible to identify the users. This category of data would include, for example, the IP addresses and domain names of the computers used by users who connect to the site, the addresses in URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) notation of the requested resources, the time of the request, the method used to submit the request to the server, the size of the file obtained in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server response (successful, error, etc.) and other parameters pertaining to the operating system and the computing environment used by the user. Calzedonia uses these data for the sole purpose of processing anonymous statistical information about the use of the websites and to control their correct operation. The data could be used to ascertain responsibility in case of possible information crimes. Except in this case, the data remain on our information systems for a period which usually does not exceed thirty days. 

BACK TO TOP

###  What are Cookies and how do we use them? 

Cookies are small text files that the websites of the Calzedonia Group may create on the device you are using to navigate. The purpose of cookies, in general, is to store and convey information. This is useful both for companies, which can, for example, use them to measure the use of their websites by the users, and for the users of the websites, by enabling them, for example, to set their personal navigation preferences (such as the choice of language). 

Calzedonia’s policy on the use of cookies envisages mainly: 

  * non systematic and generalized use, but use limited exclusively to specific circumstances and purposes; 
  * information to the users about the cookie used and collection of their informed consent when necessary. 

Calzedonia uses cookies on its websites mainly to improve your experience of navigation. For example: if you visit a screen on one of our websites and customize it, and want it to appear as you set it up the next time you visit the website, this is possible thanks to a cookie. If you want to make purchases and fill your cart but have to terminate the session or shut down your computer, at your next visit the products you had in your cart will be right there where you left them. This is possible thanks to a cookie. 

Calzedonia cannot trace back through the cookies to any of your personal data (such as first and last name, e-mail) unless you supply them directly. Moreover, another website cannot use a cookie issued by the Calzedonia website to access information contained on your computer. Once it has been saved on your computer, the cookie can only be read by the website that created it. 

If you go on reading, you will learn that the Calzedonia Group websites use different types of cookies. Some of them are essential for the operation of the website, others are not. In any case, remember: you can set the browser on your computer so as to accept all cookies, only some or none at all. 

The cookies we use can be distinguished on the basis of the amount of time they remain on the device you use for navigation, the origin and purpose for which they are used. 

####  Time on device 

**Session cookies (temporary cookies):** they are eliminated and disappear from your device when you leave the website or close the browser. 

**Permanent cookies:** they remain on the device even after you leave the website until you eliminate them or they reach their expiration date. The Calzedonia Group websites create this type of cookie and they are saved on your device so that you can read them when you visit our websites again. This enables you to find your preferences, for example, if you have entered them on the website, when you visit the website again (such as wish lists). 

####  Origin 

**First party cookies:** these are the cookies issued by the website you are visiting; the website corresponds to the address you entered (website displayed in the window of the URL). 

**Third party cookies:** these are cookies issued by a different website from the one you are visiting (for example those used by our business partners, our suppliers, or services such as Criteo or Google Analytics). 

####  Purpose 

**Strictly necessary or so-called “technical” cookies:** these cookies are essential to navigate the website you are visiting and use some of its functions. Without these cookies some of the online services you require (such as access to reserved areas, the use of the virtual shopping cart, etc.) cannot be supplied. With this type of cookie we do not gather any of your personal information and therefore have no way of identifying you. 

**Cookies for services:** these cookies gather anonymous information and help us understand how the users interact with our websites. For example, they tell us which screens are most visited, how much time people spend on the website, send us any error messages, etc. The service cookies we use only gather aggregate information in anonymous form and serve to improve the operation of the websites and your navigating experience. To know how to eliminate or manage service cookies you can see the last section of this file. 

**Cookies for functions:** these cookies enable the website to record the choices made (such as the size of the character for the text displayed, language preference, country in which the user is located, etc.) and to offer you the customized functions you have selected. In some cases, these cookies can also be used to offer online services (such as the offer of a direct chat service) or to avoid offering you messages or services you have already refused in the past. Our websites issue this type of cookie on your device in an entirely anonymous way that does not give us any possibility of identifying you. To know how to eliminate or manage cookies for functions you can see the last section of this file. We remind you that if you eliminate this type of cookie your preferences and/or settings will not be saved for your future visits. 

**Promotional cookies or cookies for targeting:** These cookies are used exclusively by the Intimissimi and Falconeri websites. The promotional cookies are used to gather information about your navigation habits, in order to send you advertising messages that correspond as much as possible to your interests. This means that we also use them to limit the number of times you will see a certain advertisement: it is the most effective way for us to communicate and for you to receive advertising that is less invasive and closer to your interests. While you navigate in the Calzedonia Group websites, the promotional cookies enable us to obtain confirmation that you are viewing our advertising messages and to show you promotional content that we think can be of your interest, based on what you have visited previously. These cookies also enable us, while you are navigating on other websites, to show you promotional content you viewed recently on the Calzedonia Group websites. Our websites use promotional cookies only in anonymous mode: we offer you targeted advertising but we don’t know who you are! The promotional cookies we use are permanent, though they only remain on your device for a limited time, and may be first or third party cookies. To know how to eliminate or manage service cookies you can see the last section of this file. 

**Refusing and blocking cookies**

The majority of web browsers are initially set to accept cookies automatically. This means that you can set the browser at any time so as to accept all cookies, only some or none at all, disabling their use by websites. In addition, you can usually set the preferences of your browser so as to be informed every time a cookie is saved on your computer. At the end of every web session, you can also cancel the cookies collected from your hard disk. If you want to eliminate the cookies installed in the cookie file of the browser used, you should know that each browser has different procedures for managing settings. 

Selecting one of the links below, you can obtain specific instructions for some of the main browsers. 

Microsoft Windows Explorer: <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies>

Google Chrome: [https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647&p=cpn_cookies](https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647&p=cpn_cookies)

Mozilla Firefox: <http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies>

Apple Safari: <http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html>

If you don’t want to receive the cookies of Google Analytics you can disable them by connecting to the link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

To find out more about cookies in general, visit the link [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

If you want to know more about behavioral advertising and online privacy, visit the link [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

If you want to know more about the cookies of Google Analytics visit <http://www.google.com/intl/it/analytics/privacyoverview.html>

If you want to know more about the Criteo cookies used by our websites, visit <http://www.criteo.com/en/privacy-policy>

**Social buttons and widgets**

You may find social buttons/widgets on the Calzedonia Group websites. These are special "buttons" showing the icons of social networks (for example, Facebook and Twitter). These “buttons” allow the users visiting the Calzedonia Group websites to reach and interact directly with the social networks with a "click". Your click on the social buttons/widgets will allow the social network to acquire the data relative to your visit. Aside from these cases, in which you spontaneously agree with your click to share the data of your web activity with your chosen social networks, Calzedonia does not share any navigation data or user data acquired through its websites with the social network accessible thanks to the social buttons/widgets. For any other information about cookies and social buttons/widgets used by our sites, please write to us at [privacy@calzedonia.it](mailto:privacy@calzedonia.it)

BACK TO TOP

###  Who do we share navigation information with? 

The data acquired during navigation may be known to other companies which provide the companies in the Calzedonia Group with computer assistance services and data processing (as in the case of activities of hosting assigned to other companies and connected with the use of our internet websites) appointed for the purposes as data processors. The data may also be known to and processed in the companies of the Calzedonia Group by personnel assigned to data processing, in the limit to which this is necessary in connection with their duties, performing only the actions necessary for such performance. In case of express request and under the circumstances authorized by law, the data may be communicated by Calzedonia to the authorities of public safety and the police forces. No navigation data is disclosed in any way. 

BACK TO TOP

###  Spontaneous e-mail transmission 

When you spontaneously send an e-mail to one of the e-mail addresses indicated on our websites, we acquire the sender’s address and any other personal data you include in the message and attachments. The e-mail addresses indicated on our websites, and any other e-mail address of the Calzedonia Group, are not personal in nature even when they bear the name and/or surname of a physical person. They belong to the business organization and their primary purpose is to permit the effective management of the business activities of the Calzedonia Group companies. This means that any messages sent to the e-mail addresses of the Calzedonia Group may be read by other people in the organization in addition to the addressee. When you send e-mail to the e-mail addresses indicated on our websites you declare that you have read and accepted the conditions of use detailed in this policy. 

BACK TO TOP

###  Compiling forms on the websites 

When you access the websites of the Calzedonia Group and decide to use its interactive services (such as requesting newsletters, registering on websites and communities, making purchases, participating in events, campaigns, etc.), you may be asked to fill out a form on the website with some of your personal data. In accordance with the provisions of art. 13 L.D. 196/03, the code on the subject of the protection of personal data, we hereby provide you with some information that will help you understand how we use the data you send us. 

BACK TO TOP

###  Mode and purpose of data processing 

To access the services and content provided by our websites, you may be asked personal data such as your first and last name, address, e-mail, credit card number, etc. We will never ask you for sensitive data on our web forms (such as your racial or ethnic origin, religious, philosophical or political believes, the state of your health, your sex life, etc.) or any judicial data (data on your police record, or relative to your position as a suspect or accused person). The data are processed by means of IT and telematic tools and hardcopy supports, in respect of the provisions of law tending to guarantee security and confidentiality, as well as accuracy, updating and relevance of the data with respect to the declared purposes. As a matter of fact, you yourself can help us ensure that your data are always accurate by communicating any changes to [privacy@calzedonia.it](mailto:privacy@calzedonia.it). The data you give us will be processed by personnel expressly designated by the Data Controller as assigned personnel and/or data processors, depending on the respective profiles of authorization assigned. The personnel appointed and their supervisors may perform operations of consultation, use, processing, comparison and any other operation, including automatic processes, only if they have been expressly authorized to do so. We use the personal data you give us only for purposes strictly connected with the individual service requested and used. Whenever we intend to use your personal data for other or different purposes from the provision of the service requested, before proceeding with processing we will request your consent. 

Hereafter we list the services available through our websites for which we ask you to provide your personal data. For each service we indicate the purpose of processing. 

**Registration for the newsletter:** the newsletter is a communication with promotional and advertising content, sent to all the interested parties who request it. On some of our websites, registration for the newsletter implies sending promotional communications that are not generalized, but are targeted on the basis of the language, sex and country of origin of the interested party. This means that we process the data we receive so as to divide the registrations into groups distinguished by language, sex and country of origin so that the newsletter sent is as close as possible to the person who requests it and could be interested. 

**Participation in exhibitions, events, contests and theme initiatives scheduled from time to time as special and temporary events:** we will use the data to enable you to participate in the specific initiatives which you may attend from time to time. 

**Registration in restricted web communities (such as My Intimissimi):** we will use the data to enable you to create your own reserved area on our websites and participate in the activities of the virtual community (such as creating wish lists, sharing your content with other users through the Calzedonia Group websites, chronology of purchase, e-mail preferences, etc.). We point out that registration in our web communities will enable you to access many of the other services on the websites more easily, but is not a required condition for using them. For example, you can receive the newsletter or make purchases even without being registered. 

**Purchase of products:** the data you give us are used to fill your purchase orders and related activities (delivery of goods, billing, management of payments and other activities.) 

**Applying for a job:** when you send your resume spontaneously, or answer an open ad, we will use your data for the necessary activities of selection and recruitment. When you fill out the web form for a job application we will provide you with specific information. 

**Requests of information or contact** (for example, requests of trade and technical information, contact requests, status of orders, availability of products, etc.): the data you give us will be used to send you only what you have requested. 

We use the data collected through the above services for the further purpose of performing statistical analyses and market surveys. This use is always made in aggregate, anonymous form, however. This means that we never relate your personal data with the data processed for statistical purposes. 

We may also use your personal data for other purposes, as described below. 

Remember: every time we plan to use your personal data for one of the purposes described hereafter, we will inform you specifically and request your express and unconditioned consent. In addition, you can withdraw your consent at any time and change the choice made by writing to [privacy@calzedonia.it](mailto:privacy@calzedonia.it). 

**Transmission of targeted communications and generalized trade offers:** we could ask your consent to use your data to send you targeted communications (such as best wishes for your birthday) or generalized advertising messages and promotions via traditional mail, e-mail, fax, text, etc. Your consent to receive these communications will be valid for communications sent using automated systems without an operator (such as e-mail or text messages) as well as for traditional means of contact (such as mail through the postal service). You may always revoke consent to the use of your data for this purposes, even separately, choosing, for example, to receive advertising only via regular mail and refusing any sent via automated systems. We inform you that the law on the protection of personal data (art. 130, section 4, L.D. 196/2003) permits so-called “soft spam”. This means that without having to obtain your express consent we can use the e-mail address you gave us on the occasion of a previous purchase, for direct sale of similar products to those you have already purchased, on condition that you do not object to such use. Aside from the case of “soft spam”, if we intend to use your personal data to send you business communications, we will specifically ask you to give your consent. 

**Analysis of consumer habits:** in some cases, we may use the data you send us to take advantage of particular services (such as requesting the newsletter or making purchases) for what is called “profiling”, which is an analysis of the social breakdown of consumers by age, sex, country of origin, profession, consumer habits, etc. Profiling involves processing the data you give us to create groups of consumers divided by market segment on the basis of a targeted set of elements (such as sex, country of origin) in order to reach more evolved profiles based on preferences, online conduct and previous purchases. This activity serves two purposes: it enables us to develop products and services with characteristics in line with the preferences of our consumers and it enables us to send advertising messages as nearly as possible geared to your tastes and interests. 

**Communication of your data to third parties:** in a few cases we ask you to give your consent to send your data to other companies in the Calzedonia Group which will send you their promotional offers and advertising. With your consent you can receive trade offers referring to products with all the trademarks of the Calzedonia Group. 

BACK TO TOP

###  Consent to use 

In all cases in which your consent is required in order to process your data, we will specifically request it for the individual purpose, expressed freely and without conditioning. We inform you, however, that for some specific purposes the law on the protection of personal data permits Calzedonia to process your data without your consent (art. 24, L.D. 196/03). This occurs, for example, when it is necessary to process your data in order to comply with the law, when it is necessary for the performance of contractual obligations accepted toward you (purchase of products, requests of services provided through the websites of the Calzedonia Group) or to comply, before stipulation of the contract, with your specific requests. 

BACK TO TOP

###  Communication and disclosure 

Calzedonia communicates your personal data to third parties exclusively when this is necessary and functional to the attainment of the purposes of use of the data pursued in function of the service requested by you, and in any case proceeds to communication only after informing you and, where necessary, obtaining your consent to do so. In general, the data collected through the individual services and for the purposes indicated herein are normally communicated to the following categories of organizations: 

  * organizations to which the right to access them is granted by law or regulations (such as public security or police forces); 
  * companies in the Calzedonia Group such as parent companies, subsidiaries and affiliates; 
  * data processing companies and providers of information services (e.g. web hosting, data entry, management and maintenance of information infrastructures and information services, e-mail marketing, Acquirer, etc.); 
  * companies and offices performing consultant services; 
  * other companies, to send their business communications only with the specific consent of the interested party. 

In particular, certain specific services provided through our website may require communication to other categories of organizations such as: 

  * purchase of products: Banca Sella, Paypal, shipping companies, financial institutions, companies performing services of mail carriers and forwarders of correspondence 
  * job applications: consultant firms for the recruitment and selection of personnel, with the purpose of supporting the Data Controller in evaluating the profiles and applicants. 

Calzedonia does not ordinarily disclose your data. Certain services provided by our websites (such as "share my wish list"), however, permit the disclosure of your personal data to other users and web network services; this is, however, left to your free choice and is only possible after your specific and voluntary initiative. In some specific cases, however, we may ask you to send us your personal data (including photographs and audio-visual material) to enable you to participate in events, competitions and theme initiatives having an extraordinary and temporary character which, by their specific nature, require communication and disclosure of data. In these cases we will inform you and ask you to give your specific consent. 

BACK TO TOP

###  Rights of interested parties 

The data subject has the right at all times to exercise the provisions of art. 7 of Legislative Decree no. 196/03. In particular, data subjects may request confirmation of the existence of their data (content and origin), verify their accuracy or request addition, updating, correction or deletion. To exercise your rights you may contact the Data Controller in the person of the IT department area manager at the main office of Calzedonia S.p.A., or by writing to [privacy@calzedonia.it](mailto:privacy@calzedonia.it). 

BACK TO TOP

###  Data controller and processor 

The controller of the data of users of all its websites: CALZEDONIA, INTIMISSIMI, TEZENIS, FALCONERI, HOTEL VERONESI LA TORRE, SIGNORVINO is Calzedonia S.p.A, with management offices at Via Monte Baldo no. 20 Dossobuono di Villafranca (VR), Italy. 

The controller of the personal data of users of the AGRIBEL websites is Società Agricola Agribel S.S., with offices at Via Fontana Parata, 8 00040 Lanuvio (Rome), Italy. To exercise their rights and for further information concerning data processing, interested parties may contact the controller by writing to the address [privacy@agribel.it](mailto:privacy@agribel.it)

BACK TO TOP
